Greater Hartford Jewish Community Center Collection 0008.120.001
Jewish Historical Society of Greater Hartford
Youth Services/Teens/College preparation program
Youth Services/Teens/Miscellaneous, 1950s and earlier
Youth Services/Teens/Miscellaneous, 1960s
Youth Services/Teens/Miscellaneous, 1970s
Youth Services/Teens/Miscellaneous, 1980s
Youth Services/Teens/Miscellaneous, 1990s
Youth Services/Teens/Miscellaneous, undated
Youth Services/Teens/new teen lounge, 1980
Youth Services/Teens/Theater program, 2 folders
Youth Services/Teens/Travel
- Series I: Adult Education
  - Adult Education/Adult Education Committee, 1995
  - Adult Education/Adult Education Committee/Jewish Enrichment Committee, 1980s-1990s, undated
  - Adult Education/Courses, undated
  - Adult Education/Co-wed club, undated
  - Adult Education/Multicultural programs, undated
  - Adult Education/Hebrew classes, undated
  - Adult Education/Holiday events/Chanukah, undated
  - Adult Education/Holiday events/Miscellaneous, undated
  - Adult Education/Holiday events/Passovers, undated
  - Adult Education/Holiday events/Purim, undated
  - Adult Education/Holiday events/Rosh Hashanah, undated
  - Adult Education/Holiday events/Tu Ba'shvat, undated
  - Adult Education/Jewish birth baskets, undated
  - Adult Education/Kolot (Choir), undated
  - Adult Education/Kosher Culinary Institute, undated
  - Adult Education/Lectures, undated
  - Adult Education/Miscellaneous, undated
  - Adult Education/New Mothers' group, undated
  - Adult Education/Sabbath, undated
  - Adult Education/Saturday Eve-ers, undated
  - Adult Education/Synagogue and Jewish Organization Fair, 1989
  - Adult Education/Travel, undated
  - Adult Education/Yiddish Cultural Club, undated
  - Adult Education/Yiddish Programs, undated
  - Adult Education/Yom Hashoah (Holocaust Remembrance Day), undated
  - Adult Education/Young Adults and Singles, undated
- Series II: Cultural Arts
  - Cultural Arts (Including Ann Randall Committee)/Art Exhibits. See also Sephardic programs., undated
  - Cultural Arts (Including Ann Randall Committee)/Art Exhibits, undated
  - Cultural Arts (Including Ann Randall Committee)/Art Exhibits/Newspaper clippings, undated
  - Cultural Arts/Art Exhibits, 2000s
  - Cultural Arts/Art Exhibits/Goldenthal, Jolene, art critic at Hartford Courant/Newspaper articles, 1970-1980, undated
  - Cultural Arts (Including Ann Randall Committee)/Classes, undated
  - Cultural Arts (Including Ann Randall Committee)/Concerts, undated
  - Cultural Arts (Including Ann Randall Committee)/Dance, undated
  - Cultural Arts (Including Ann Randall Committee)/Fundraising, undated
  - Cultural Arts (Including Ann Randall Committee)/Jewish Musical Festival, undated
  - Cultural Arts/Literature, undated
  - Cultural Arts (Including Ann Randall Committee)/Miscellaneous Events, undated
  - Cultural Arts (Including Ann Randall Committee)/Poetry, undated
  - Cultural Arts (Including Ann Randall Committee)/Program Listing, undated
  - Cultural Arts (Including Ann Randall Committee)/Randall, Ann, undated
  - Cultural Arts (Including Ann Randall Committee)/Theater and Cinema (includes dvds of plays), undated
  - Cultural Arts (Including Ann Randall Committee)/Travel Programs, undated
  - Cultural Arts/(Including Ann Randall Committee)/Randall, Ann Heilpern, biographical information, undated
  - Cultural Arts/Committee, undated
  - Cultural Arts/Hartford Jewish Film festival, 1996-2007
  - Cultural Arts/Sephardic Programs, undated
  - Cultural Arts/Tribute to Anne Frank, 1984
- Series III: General Administration
  - General Administration/Anniversaries/80th, 1995
  - General Administration/Anniversaries/85th, 1999
  - General Administration/Anniversaries/Jewish Tercentenary Year, 1954
  - General Administration/Annual Meeting Invitations, undated
  - General Administration/Annual Meeting Newspaper clippings, undated
  - General Administration/Annual Meeting Programs, 1950s
  - General Administration/Annual Meeting Programs, 1960s
  - General Administration/Annual Meeting Programs, 1970s
  - General Administration/Annual Meeting Programs, 1980s
  - General Administration/Annual Meeting Programs, 1990s
  - General Administration/Annual Meeting Programs, 2000s
  - General Administration/Annual Reports, 1990s-2000s, 1990-2000
  - General Administration/Awards, undated
- Series IV: General Administration: Board of Directors
  - General Administration/Board of Directors/Members, see also Annual Meetings, undated
  - General Administration/Board of Directors/Minutes, undated
  - General Administration/Board of Directors/Miscellaneous, undated
  - General Administration/Board of Directors/Planning/1982 Oct., Study of "Directions and Priorities"
  - General Administration/Board of Directors/Planning/1983 March, Capital Needs Committee Report
  - General Administration/Board of Directors/Planning/1984 Study under JWB Auspices
  - General Administration/Board of Directors/Planning/1988 United Way Agency Self-assessment Study
  - General Administration/Board of Directors/Planning/1990 member and Community Survey
  - General Administration/Board of Directors/Planning/SWOT Analysis, 2002
  - General Administration/Board of Directors/Policies/Miscellaneous, undated
  - General Administration/Board of Directors/Policies/Saturday (Shabbat) Opening, 1962
  - General Administration/Board of Directors/Policies/Saturday (Shabbat) opening, 1981
  - General Administration/Board of Directors/Policies/Saturday (Shabbat) Opening, 1992-1994
  - General Administration/Board of Directors/Policies/Saturday (Shabbat) Opening, 2007
  - General Administration/Board of Directors/Presidents, undated
- Series V: General Administration: Buildings
  - General Administration/Buildings/1015 Asylum Ave., Hartford, 1949
  - General Administration/Buildings/335 Bloomfield Ave, W. H., 1962, 3 folders
  - General Administration/Buildings/335 Bloomfield Ave., W. Hartford/Plans, undated
  - General Administration/Buildings/335 Bloomfield Ave, W. H. /Expansion, 1990, 2 folders
  - General Administration/Buildings/335 Bloomfield Ave., W.H./Architects Collaborative/construction reports, 1962
  - General Administration/Buildings/335 Bloomfield Ave., W.H./Expansion/Groundbreaking, 1989
  - General Administration/Buildings/335 Bloomfield Ave., W.H./Horn Construction Company/contract and related documents, 1960
  - General Administration/Buildings/335 Bloomfield Ave., W.H./Planning/Committees, 1960s
  - General Administration/Buildings/335 Bloomfield Ave., W.H./Planning/Minutes of Meetings, late 1950s-early 1960s, 1950-1960
  - General Administration/Buildings/335 Bloomfield Ave., W.H./Scrapbook about planning and construction, 1960s
- Series VI: General Administration: Buildings
  - General Administration/Buildings/335 Bloomfield Ave, W. H. /Second renovation/2000s
  - General Administration/Buildings/Mandel building/Fundraising, 2000s
- Series VII: General Administration: C – F
  - General Administration/Calendar, undated
  - General Administration/Constitution and By-Laws, undated
  - General Administration/Financial Records, 1980s, 1980-1989
  - General Administration/Financial Records, 1990s, 1990-1999
  - General Administration/Financial Records, 2000s, 2000-2010
  - General Administration/Founding, undated
  - General Administration/Fundraising/Annual Scholarship and Gala/1980s
  - General Administration/Fundraising/Annual Scholarship and Gala/1990s
  - General Administration/Fundraising/Annual Scholarship and Gala/2000s
  - General Administration/Fundraising/Annual Scholarship Fund/Taste of the Town, 2000s
  - General Administration/Fundraising/Building Campaign, 1986-1990, 2 folders
  - General Administration/Fundraising/Leadership, undated
  - General Administration/Fundraising/Miscellaneous, undated
- Series VIII: General Administration: G - Z
  - General Administration/Historical Highlights, undated
  - General Administration/JWB and JCC Association Magazines, undated
  - General Administration/Membership/Membership Studies, undated
  - General Administration/Membership/Miscellaneous, undated
  - General Administration/Membership/Promotional Materials, undated
  - General Administration/Miscellaneous, undated
  - General Administration/Mission Statements, undated
  - General Administration/Program and Administrative Studies, 1950s-1960s, 1950-1969
  - General Administration/Public Relations and Marketing, undated
  - General Administration/Staff/Minutes and Memos, undated
  - General Administration/Staff/Job Descriptions, undated
  - General Administration/Staff Members/Jacobs, David L., undated
  - General Administration/Staff Members/Kaplan, Theodore N., undated
  - General Administration/Staff Members/Leipzig, Jay, undated
  - General Administration/Staff Members/Margolis, Jed, undated
  - General Administration/Staff Members/Marks, Sheila, undated
  - General Administration/Staff Members/Miscellaneous, undated
  - General Administration/Staff Members/Newman, Brian, undated
  - General Administration/Staff Members/Shapiro, Murray, undated
  - General Administration/Staff Members/Wyckoff, Karen, undated
  - General Administration/Volunteers, undated
- Series IX: Health and Fitness
  - Health and Fitness/GHJCC Swim and Tennis Club, undated
  - Health and Fitness/Maccabi Games, 1997
  - Health and Fitness/Maccabi Games/Miscellaneous, undated
  - Health and Fitness/Miscellaneous, undated
  - Health and fitness/Surveys and planning, 1980s, 1980-1989
- Series X: Program Catalogs: 1940s-1980
  - Program Catalogs/1940s-1950s, 1940-1959
  - Program Catalogs/1963-1964
  - Program Catalogs/1964-1965
  - Program Catalogs/1967-1968
  - Program Catalogs/1968-1969
  - Program Catalogs/1969-1970
  - Program Catalogs/1970-1971
  - Program Catalogs/1971-1972
  - Program Catalogs/1972-1973
  - Program Catalogs/1973-1974
  - Program Catalogs/1974-1975
  - Program Catalogs/1975-1976
  - Program Catalogs/1976-1977
  - Program Catalogs/1977-1978
  - Program Catalogs/1978-1979
  - Program Catalogs/1979-1980
- Series XI: Program Catalogs, 1980s - 1990s
  - Program Catalogs/1980-1981
  - Program Catalogs/1981-1982
  - Program Catalogs/1982-1983
  - Program Catalogs/1983-1984
  - Program Catalogs/1984-1985
  - Program Catalogs/1985-1986
  - Program Catalogs/1986-1987
  - Program Catalogs/1987-1988
  - Program Catalogs/1988, 1988-1989
  - Program Catalogs/1989-1990
  - Program Catalogs/1992, no catalog, newspaper clippings only
  - Program Catalogs/1995
  - Program Catalogs/1996
  - Program Catalogs/1997
  - Program Catalogs/1998
  - Program Catalogs/1999
- Series XII: Program Catalogs, 2000s
  - Program Catalogs/2000
  - Program Catalogs/2001
  - Program Catalogs/2001-2002
  - Program Catalogs/2002-2003
  - Program Catalogs/2003
  - Program Catalogs/2004
  - Program Catalogs/2005
- Series XIII: Senior Adults, A-N
  - Senior Adults/Activities and Programs, 1950s-1970s, 1950-1970
  - Senior Adults/Activities and Programs, 1980s-1990s, 1980-1990
  - Senior Adults/Community Action Committee, 1970s, 1970-1979
  - Senior Adults/Eastern Suburbs, undated
  - Senior Adults/Education Programs, undated
  - Senior Adults/Escort Project, 1978
  - Senior Adults/Extension Programs and Sites, 1960s-1970s, 1960-1979
  - Senior Adults/Forms/Miscellaneous, undated
  - Senior Adults/Friendly Social Club/Constitution, undated
  - Senior Adults/Friendly Social Club/Members, undated
  - Senior Adults/Friendly Social Club/Miscellaneous, undated
  - Senior Adults/Friendly Social Club/Newsletter, 1957-1968
  - Senior Adults/Friendly Social Club/Newsletter, 1974-1978
  - Senior Adults/Friendly Social Club/Officers, 1970s, 1970-1979
  - Senior Adults/Friendly Social Club/Programs, 1959-1985
  - Senior Adults/Friendly Social Club/Scrapbook, 1955-1977 OVERSIZE
  - Senior Adults/Gym and Swim Program, undated
  - Senior Adults/Health Services, undated
  - Senior Adults/Historical Highlights, undated
  - Senior Adults/Intergenerational programs, undated
  - Senior Adults/Leisure Lounge, undated
  - Senior Adults/Men's Club, undated
  - Senior Adults/Miscellaneous, undated
  - Senior Adults/New Britain Seniors/Miscellaneous, undated
  - Senior Adults/New Britain Seniors/Newsletter, 1970s-80s, 1970-1989
  - Senior Adults/Newcomers Group, undated
- Series XIV: Senior Adults, O-Z
  - Senior Adults/Older Adult Program/Committee/Members, 1970s, 1970-1979
  - Senior Adults/Older Adult Program/Minutes, 1974-1979
  - Senior Adults/Older Adult Program/Minutes, 1980s, 1980-1989
  - Senior Adults/Older Adult Program/Newsletter, 1957-1959
  - Senior Adults/Older Adult Program/Newsletter, 1979-1981
  - Senior Adults/Older Adult Program/Planning and Budgets, 1970s-1980s, 1970-1989
  - Senior Adults/Older Adult Program/Reports and Evaluations, 1950s-1960s, 1950-1969
  - Senior Adults/Older Adult Program/Reports and Evaluations, 1980s, 1980-1989
  - Senior Adults/Older Adult Program/Registration Forms, 1965-1968
  - Senior Adults/Planning/Studies, undated
  - Senior Adults/Retired Seniors Council, undated
- Series XV: Senior Adults/Scrapbooks
  - Senior Adults/Older Adult Program/Scrapbook, 1964-1965
  - Senior Adults/Older Adult Program/Scrapbook, 1966-1967
  - Senior Adults/Older Adult Program/Scrapbook, 1968-1969
  - Senior Adults/Older Adult Program/Scrapbook, 1967-1968
  - Senior Adults/Older Adult Program/Scrapbook, 1968-1969
- Series XVI: Senior Adults/ S-Z
  - Senior adults/Senior Breakfast Club, undated
  - Senior Adults/Senior Housing, 1970s, 1970-1979
  - Senior Adults/Senior Power/Members, 1970s, 1970-1979
  - Senior Adults/Senior Power/Miscellaneous, 1970s, 1970-1979
  - Senior Adults/Senior Power/Newsletter, 1970s, 1970-1979
  - Senior Adults/Senior Volunteer Corps/Miscellaneous, undated
  - Senior Adults/SES/Constitution and By-laws, undated
  - Senior Adults/SES/members, 1960s-1970s, 1960-1979
  - Senior Adults/SES/Minutes, 1974
  - Senior Adults/SES/minutes, 1975
  - Senior Adults/SES/Minutes, 1976-1977
  - Senior Adults/SES/Minutes, 1977-1978
  - Senior Adults/SES/Miscellaneous, 1974
  - Senior Adults/SES/Newsletter, 1974-1978
  - Senior Adults/SES/Officers, 1970s, 1970-1979
  - Senior Adults/SES/Play scripts, 1970s, 1970-1979
  - Senior Adults/SES/Programs, 1970s-1980s, 1970-1989
  - Senior Adults/SES II/Constitution and By-Laws, 1978
  - Senior Adults/SES II/Members, 1970s, 1970-1979
  - Senior Adults/SES II/Minutes, 1974-1975
  - Senior Adults/SES II/Minutes, 1977-1977
  - Senior Adults/SES II/Minutes, 1977-1978
  - Senior Adults/SES II/Miscellaneous, 1970s, 1970-1979
  - Senior Adults/SES II/Newsletter, 1975-1978
  - Senior Adults/Singles, undated
  - Senior Adults/Staff, 1970s, 1970-1979
  - Senior Adults/Sunday for Seniors, 1970s-1980s, 1970-1989
  - Senior Adults/Telephone Reassurance Program, 1977
  - Senior Adults/Theater program/Correspondence, 1970s, 1970-1979
  - Senior Adults/Theater program/programs, 1970s, 1970-1979
  - Senior Adults/Theater program/publicity, 1970s-1980, 1970-1989
  - Senior Adults/Theater program/schedule, 1970-1980s, 1970-1989
  - Senior Adults/Transportation, 1970s, 1970-1979
  - Senior Adults/Travel, 1974-1981
  - Senior Adults/Travel, 1990s-2000s, 1990-2010
  - Senior Adults/Volunteers/miscellaneous, undated
- Series XVII: Mixed Media
  - Miscellaneous newspaper clippings, undated
  - Book festival, undated
  - Book festival, 2006
  - Book festival 2011, 10 year anniversary (includes 2 DVDs)
  - Camp Shalom and Camp Keshet/Miscellaneous, undated
  - Camp Shalom and Camp Keshet/Newspaper clippings, undated
  - Camp Shalom and Camp Keshet/Publicity and Catalogs, undated
  - Committees/New Leadership, 1980s, 1980-1989
  - Early Childhood Center/Camp Rennah, Campareenah, undated
  - Early Childhood Center/Miscellaneous, undated
  - Early Childhood Center/Newspaper clippings, 2000s, 2000-2010
  - Holocaust Events sponsored by JCC (see also JHSGH's Holocaust Collection, undated
  - Interfaith programs, undated
  - Israel Affairs/Halimi, Ilan/vigil, 2006
  - Israel Affairs/Israel's 30th anniversary, 1978
  - Israel Affairs/Israel's 40th anniversary, 1988
  - Israel Affairs/Israel's 50th anniversary, 1998
  - Israel Affairs/Israel's' anniversaries, miscellaneous, undated
  - Israel Affairs/Israeli Folk Dancing, undated
  - Israel Affairs/Jerusalem, undated
  - Israel Affairs/Let's Go Israel, undated
  - Israel Affairs/Miscellaneous, undated
  - Israel Affairs/Shaliach, undated
  - Israel Affairs/Yom Ha'atzmaut (Independence Day), undated
  - Israel Affairs/Yom Hazikaron (Israel Remembrance Day), undated
  - Maccabean Games, undated
  - Race Relations, undated
  - Shabbat, 1980s, 1980-1989
  - Security, undated
  - September 11, 2001/Responses and Memorials
  - Soviet Jewry/Miscellaneous, undated
  - Special Needs/Miscellaneous, undated
  - Youth Services/children (see also Adult Education/Holidays), undated
  - Youth Services/College Students, undated
  - Youth Services/Jonathan's Dream playground (Barzach-Jaffe family, boundless playgrounds), undated
  - Youth Services/Teens (see also Cultural Arts/Theater and Cinema), undated
- Series XVIII: Newsletters
  - Newsletters/JCC Journal/1940s, 1940-1949
  - Newsletters/Scope/1950s, 1950-1959
  - Newsletters/Scope/1960s, 1960-1969
  - Newsletters/Scope/1970 1973
  - Newsletters/Scope/1974 1976
  - Newsletters/Center Fold/1977 May - 1979, 1977-1979
  - Newsletters/Center Fold/1980 1984
  - Newsletters/1985 1989
  - Newsletters/OnCenter/before 2000/OVERSIZE: Box 1
  - Newsletters/OnCenter/2000s/OVERSIZE: Box 2, 2000-2010
- Series XIX: Artifacts
  - Paperweight, 1989, in miscellaneous artifact box with Hart family artifacts, etc.
- Photo Series I: Camps: Keshet, Macabee, Moshava, Naomi, Reenah, Shalom, New Hartford
  - Camps/Camp Keshet, undated
  - Camps/Camp Macabee, undated
  - Camps/Camp Moshava, undated
  - Camps/Camp Naomi, undated
  - Camps/Camp Reenah, Campareenah see GHJCC/Early Childhood Center, undated
  - Camps/Camp Shalom, New Hartford/(see also photos/organizations/Jewish Children's Service Organization, undated
  - Camps/Camp Shalom, New Hartford/Administration and Staff, undated
  - Camps/Camp Shalom, New Hartford/Activities/Boating, undated
  - Camps/Camp Shalom, New Hartford/Activities/Buildings and Grounds, undated
  - Camps/Camp Shalom, New Hartford/Activities/Carnival, undated
  - Camps/Camp Shalom, New Hartford/Activities/Crafts, undated
  - Camps/Camp Shalom, New Hartford/Flood Damage, undated
  - Camps/Camp Shalom, New Hartford/Fundraising, undated
  - Camps/Camp Shalom, New Hartford/Fundraising, undated
  - Camps/Camp Shalom, New Hartford/Miscellaneous, 3 folders, undated
  - Camps/Camp Shalom, New Hartford/Activities/Nature, undated
  - Camps/Camp Shalom, New Hartford/Activities/Swimming, undated
- Photo Series Ia: Camps: Shalom, Windsor
  - Camps/Camp Shalom, Windsor/Administration, undated
  - Camps/Camp Shalom, Windsor/Activities/Animals, undated
  - Camps/Camp Shalom, Windsor/Activities/Archery, undated
  - Camps/Camp Shalom, Windsor/Activities/Baseball, undated
  - Camps/Camp Shalom, Windsor/Activities/Boating and River Sports, undated
  - Camps/Camp Shalom, Windsor/Activities/Campfires and Cookouts, undated
  - Camps/Camp Shalom, Windsor/Activities/Carnival, undated
  - Camps/Camp Shalom, Windsor/Activities/Crafts, undated
  - Camps/Camp Shalom, Windsor/Activities/Horseback Riding, undated
  - Camps/Camp Shalom, Windsor/Activities/Jewish Rituals, undated
  - Camps/Camp Shalom, Windsor/Activities/Miscellaneous - sports, undated
  - Camps/Camp Shalom, Windsor/Activities/Miscellaneous, 3 folders, undated
  - Camps/Camp Shalom, Windsor/Activities/Ropes course, undated
  - Camps/Camp Shalom, Windsor/Activities/Swimming, undated
  - Camps/Camp Shalom, Windsor/Activities/Tennis, undated
  - Camps/Camp Shalom, Windsor/Activities/Theatrics, undated
  - Camps/Camp Shalom, Windsor/Activities/Windsor, undated
  - Camps/Camp Shalom, Windsor/Buildings and Grounds, undated
  - Camps/Camp Shalom, Windsor/Donors, undated
  - Camps/Camp Shalom, Windsor/Fundraising, undated
  - Camps/Camp Shalom, Windsor/Staff and Counselors, undated
  - Camps/Miscellaneous, undated
- Photo Series II: Adult Education, Book Festival, Cultural Arts
  - Adult Education/Bridge Classes, undated
  - Adult Education/College Age, undated
  - Adult Education/Holidays/Chanukah, undated
  - Adult Education/Holidays/High Holy Days, undated
  - Adult Education/Holidays/Pesach, undated
  - Adult Education/Holidays/Purim, undated
  - Adult Education/Holidays/Sukkoth, undated
  - Adult Education/Miscellaneous, three folders, undated
  - Adult Education/Singles and Young Adults, undated
  - Adult Education/Soviet Jewry, undated
  - Adult Education/Yom Hashoah, undated
  - Book Festival, undated
  - Cultural Arts/Art Classes, undated
  - Cultural Arts/Art Exhibits, undated
  - Cultural Arts/Concerts, undated
  - Cultural Arts/Dance, undated
  - Cultural Arts/Gala, undated
  - Cultural Arts/Jewish Music Festival, undated
  - Cultural Arts/Miscellaneous, undated
  - Cultural Arts/Ann Randall Committee/Theater/Center Players, undated and 1950s, 1950-1959
  - Cultural Arts/Ann Randall Committee/Theater/Center Players, 1960s, 1960-1969
  - Cultural Arts/Ann Randall Committee/Theater/Center Players, 1970s, 1970-1979
  - Cultural Arts/Ann Randall Committee/Theater/Center Players, 1980s, 1980-1989
  - Cultural Arts/Ann Randall Committee/Theater/Center Players, 1990s, 1990-1999
  - Cultural Arts/Local Theater/2007, undated
  - Cultural Arts/Professional Companies, undated
  - Cultural Arts/Travel, undated
- Photo Series III: Health and Fitness, Israel Affairs, Special Needs
  - Health and Fitness/Adult Programs/Classes, undated
  - Health and Fitness/Adult Programs/Fitness rooms and health club, undated
  - Health and Fitness/Adult Programs/Runners and Joggers, undated
  - Health and Fitness/Pool, undated
  - Health and Fitness/Miscellaneous, undated
  - Health and Fitness/Racquetball, undated
  - Health and Fitness/Youth Programs/Classes, undated
  - Health and Fitness/Youth Programs/Maccabi Games, undated
  - Health and Fitness/Youth Programs/Miscellaneous, undated
  - Health and Fitness/Israel Affairs/Folk dancing, undated
  - Health and Fitness/Israel Affairs/Folk dancing/Or Chadash, undated
  - Health and Fitness/Youth Programs/Preschool, undated
  - Health and Fitness/Youth Programs/Swimming, undated
  - Health and Fitness/Youth Programs/Teams, undated
  - Israel Affairs/Israel Teen visitors, undated
  - Isreal Affairs/Iztak Rabin visits JCC 1977
  - Israel Affairs/Let's Go Israel, undated
  - Israel Affairs/Miscellaneous, undated
  - Israel Affairs/Shaliach, undated
  - Israel Affairs/Trips, undated
  - Israel Affairs/Walkathon, undated
  - Israel Affairs/Yom Haatzmaut (Independence Day), undated
  - Israel Affairs/Yom Hazikaron (Remembrance Day), undated
  - Special Needs/Athletics, undated
  - Special Needs/Sunday Afternoon Group, undated
- Photo Series IV: Senior Adults
  - Senior Adults/Arts and Crafts, undated
  - Senior Adults/Bingo and Cards, undated
  - Senior Adults/Choraliers, undated
  - Senior Adults/Education, undated
  - Senior Adults/Extension programs and sites, undated
  - Senior Adults/folk dancing, undated
  - Senior Adults/Fundraising, undated
  - Senior Adults/gym and swim program, undated
  - Senior Adults/Health Services, undated
  - Senior Adults/Holiday Programs/B'Nai b'rith Chanukah Party, undated
  - Senior Adults/Holiday Programs/Chanukah parties/sponsor unknown, undated
  - Senior Adults/Holiday Programs/NCJW Chanukah Luncheons, undated
  - Senior Adults/Holiday Programs/Miscellaneous, undated
  - Senior Adults/Lieberman, Joseph, visit, 1980
  - Senior Adults/Miscellaneous, pre-1962, undated
  - Senior Adults/Miscellaneous, post-1962, 2 folders, undated
  - Senior Adults/Programs with children, undated
  - Senior Adults/Staff training, undated
  - Senior Adults/theater, undated
  - Senior Adults/travel, undated